AsyncTasks are great for a lot of things, but they're not the best choice
AsyncTasks 适用于处理许多事情 但对于更新用户界面的数据来说
for updating data in a user interface, for that we need a Loader.
却不是最佳选择 对此 我们需要使用 Loader
Loaders solved the problems introduced in the previous video.
Loader 解决了之前视频中 介绍的问题
First, no matter how many times you request data from a loader,
首先 无论你从 loader 上 请求多少次数据
by default the Loader will only fetch the data once.
默认情况下 Loader 仅获取 一次数据
No spawning zillions of AsyncTasks and activities.
因此不会生成大量的 AsyncTasks 和活动
Second, when an activity is shut down, it'll automatically tell
其次 当一个活动停止时 它会自动告知
all its Loaders to quit what they're doing, since the data won't be used.
所有 Loader 退出正在进行的任务 因为数据不可用
Finally, Loaders persist across activity configuration changes like rotations.
最后 Loader 会始终保留整个活动的 配置更改 如旋转
So if we kick off a Loader to go fetch data and the phone is rotated,
当我们启用 Loader 获取数据时 电话旋转
the loader will automatically return its data to the new activity when it's done.
获取数据后 Loader 会自动将数据 返回至新的 Activity
Let's look at the developer guide for Loaders.
让我们看一下 Loaders 开发者指南
These components in the Android framework are specifically designed for
Android 框架中的这些组件专门用于 加载显示、Activity 或框架
loading up data for display and activities or fragments.
的数据
I've included a link below so
我在下面给出了一个链接
you can read it through in more detailed on your own.
你可以浏览该链接 阅读更多的详细信息
We'll begin with the section called Starting a Loader.
我们从名为“启动 Loader” 的部分开始
Within your activity,
在 Activity 中
you can start a Loader with the help of the LoaderManager.
你可以借助 LoaderManager 启动 Loader
Every intro activity comes equipped with a LoaderManager which takes care of
每个 intro activity 都配有一个 LoaderManager
creating, reusing, and destroying a set of loaders at the appropriate time.
可在适当的时间创建、重新使用和销毁 一组 loader
Once we get a reference to the LoaderManager,
引用 LoaderManager  后
we can now call the initLoader method.
可以调用 initLoader 方法
This first input is unique integer identifier.
第一个输入是特殊的 整数标识符
In this case, we use 0,
在本例子中 我们使用 0
this idea can be any random number as it only really matters when you have
你可以使用任意值 仅当应用中
multiple loaders in an app and need to distinguish between them.
存在多个 Loader 时 需要使用不同的值对其加以区分
The other two parameters are one, and additional bundle of inputs to Loader
其他两个参数是一体的 Loader 的其他输入包
which is null in this case, and a loader call back object.
在本例子中为 null 且 loader 回调对象
Now, we specify this for the LoaderCallbacks object,
现在 我们为 LoaderCallbacks 对象 指定此参数
because it's common for the current activity, which this refers to,
因为它在当前活动中 最为常用
to implement the LoaderCallbacks interface.
我们可以使用它 执行 LoaderCallbacks 接口
So the activity itself is the LoaderCallback object that we want to
因此活动本身是我们要 传入的 LoaderCallback
pass in.
对象
We'll talk more about the LoaderCallbacks later, but
稍后 我们会详细讨论 LoaderCallbacks
I want you to understand that the initLoader call
但是你要知道 调用 initLoader 时
ensures that the loader is both initialized and active.
必须确保 loader 处于初始化和活跃状态
So if a Loader with a given ID, say this ID's 0 already exists,
如果 Loader 已具备给定 ID 而且该 ID 的 0 已经存在
then we will reuse that last Loader.
那么我们将使用上一个 Loader
Now, if the Loader with the ID doesn't already exist, then the LoaderCallback,
如果具备 ID 的 Loader 不存在 则将触发 LoaderCallback
onCreateLoader() method will be triggered,
onCreateLoader() 方法
which will return a new Loader.
并返回一个新的 Loader
Now, it's this behavior of reusing existing Loaders that's completely
重新使用现有 Loader 的 行为是完全
essential.
有必要的
So when we rotate the device over and over again, the same
当我们反复旋转设备时 将使用相同的 Loader
Loader will be used instead of creating a new one on each orientation change.
而不是在每次变换方向时 都创建新的 Loader
So how does the Loader get created?
那么 如何创建 Loader 呢?
Well we as the developer are the lucky ones that need to define this behavior.
作为开发人员 我们感到很荣幸 可以通过执行
By implementing the LoaderCallbacks interface.
LoaderCallback 接口 定义该行为
Our activity needs to override the following three callback methods
要与 LoaderManager 进行交互
in order to interact with the LoaderManager.
活动需要覆盖 以下三种回调方法
When the onCreateLoader() method is called, we need to create and return
调用 onCreateLoader() 方法时 需要创建和返回新的 Loader 对象
a new Loader object which will fetch the earthquake data from the web server.
该对象将从 Web 服务器 获取地震数据
The onLoadFinished() method is called when the Loader is finished loading data
当 Loader 在后台线程完成数据加载后 将调用 onLoadFinished()
on the background thread.
方法
This is a good place to update UI with the list of earthquakes.
后台线程是一个更新 地震列表 UI 的好地方
The onLoaderReset() method gets called when the previous created loader
在对之前创建的 loader 进行重置时 将调用 onLoaderReset()
is being reset.
方法
So in this case the data from the last load is now invalid and
本例子中 上次加载的数据 现在已经失效
should not be use anymore.
不应该再次使用
For example,
例如
the loader maybe reset if we decide to fetch data from a different URL.
如果从其他的 URL 中获取数据 可能需要重置 loader
In this case, then the existing earthquake data is no longer valid.
在这种情况下 现有的 地震数据无效
So in this method, we typically clear out the data from the last load,
使用该方法时 我们要特别清除 上次加载的数据
which means we should clear out the earthquakes from the list.
也就是说需要从列表中 清除地震
Just as a little reminder, when you see callback methods like these,
这只是一个很小的提示 当你查看这些类似回调的方法时
this is a sign that there is asynchronous behavior.
这只是一个迹象  表明出现了异步行为
So remember that asynchronous means that the system can move on to do other
请记住 异步表示 数据未完全从 Loader 加载之前
work before the data is fully loaded from the Loader.
系统就开始进行 其他工作
Now, we create a Loader only when the system calls us back
现在 仅当系统通过 onCreateLoader()
via the onCreateLoader() method, then the system can go to do other work.
方法回调时 创建 Loader
We only update the UI when the system calls us on the onLoadFinished()
仅当系统使用 Loader 结果 调用 onLoadFinished() 时
with the Loader result.
创建 UI
There can be a short amount of time or
调用所需的时间并不固定
a lot amount of time in between each of these callbacks.
有的时间很长 有的时间很短
In the next video, we'll get into the nitty gritty details of the code
在下个视频中 我们将从根本上了解 代码的详细信息
as well as how to actually create a Loader.
以及如何实际 创建 Loader
But for now, I just want to make sure that you understand the high level
在此之前 我只想确定 你是否已经了解
benefits of Loaders.
Loader 的高级优势
In this blog post by Google eDveloper Advocate Ian Lake,
Google 开发人员倡导者 Ian Lake 在其发表的博客中谈到
he talks about the best practice for loading data into an app.
最好的实践就是将加载数据 实施到应用中
In this section, he highlights What's so special about Loaders?
在这一部分中 他强调了 Loader 的特别之处
Upon device rotation, even though your activity is recreated,
旋转设备时 即使活动是重新创建的
a Loader will survive and the data you just fetched will stick around too.
Loader 也会继续运行 且获取的数据不会丢失
So you don't have to do another expensive network call.
这样一来 你无需拨打昂贵的 网络电话
And even better, Loaders won't stay around forever.
更妙的是 Loader 不会一直保留
If the activity is destroyed, the Loader will be automatically cleaned up.
如果活动销毁 则 Loader 也将自动清除
They're actually tied to the activity life cycle,
实际上 Loader 的生命与 活动的生命周期紧密相联
and are much more appropriate for fetching data that
且 Loader 更适合用于 获取需要在屏幕上
needs to be displayed on-screen even if the activity dies.
显示的数据 即使活动不存在
A Loader though lives as long as the activity lives so
只要活动存在 Loader 就存在
a Loader is what we need.
所以 这样的 Loader 正是我们所需要的
&gt;&gt; Okay, whew, that was a fire hose of information.
好吧 这就像一个 信息的消防水带
Now, I know it's hard to keep all of that straight in your head.
我知道 你很难一下子记住 全部的内容
So I've summarized the key points in this quiz, but left the blanks for
所以在本次测验中 我总结了几个关键点 但同时留出几处空白
you to fill in.
需要你来填写
Go ahead and help me fill in the blanks.
来吧 帮我把空白处填写完整吧
What interacts with an activity to manage one or more Loader instances?
要管理一个或多个 Loader 实例 哪些内容需要与活动进行交互?
In order for an Activity to be a client that interacts with the LoaderManager,
为了让活动成为与 LoaderManager 交互的客户端
we need the EarthquakeActivity to implement the blank interface.
我们需要 EarthquakeActivity 来执行空白接口
Then the Activity must override the blank method to create and
活动必须覆盖空白方法 以便于创建和返回
return a new Loader instance.
新的 Loader 实例
The blank method to receive the data once the Loader has finished loading it.
在 Loader 完成加载后 使用空白方法来接收数据
And lastly, the blank method to handle when the previously created Loader
还有 当不再使用之前创建的 Loader 时 可以使用空白方法
is no longer needed, unless the existing data can be discarded.
进行处理 除非 现有数据可以丢弃
And lastly, to start a Loader, and
最后一题 当使用
trigger the Loader callback methods, when the app is launched,
EarthquakeActivity onCreate() 方法 启动应用时
in the EarthquakeActivity onCreate() method, we should call, what?
我们应该调用哪些内容以启动 Loader 并触发 Loader 回调?
If you need a hint, I've included possible answer choices that you can
如果需要提示 我已经在测验下方 给出了可能的答案选项
pick from in the notes below the quiz.
你可以从中选取正确的选项
So feel free to reference the documentation links, and
可以随意引用文档链接 和 Loader 的
the Loader's development guide as well.
开发指南